tickpick.com 2019-05-29

# TickPick | Privacy Policy

What Information Is Collected? **1.) Information we collect when you use our Site and Services:** We may collect information about the way you interact with our Site, including your computer, browser, and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from our sites, ad data, IP addresses, telephone calls with us, and standard web log information.  We may obtain information from or about you in other ways. For example, we may verify user information with a service provider or combine your information with information we collect from other companies. Also, we collect the information you send to us such as correspondence, customer satisfaction surveys or customer service communications, testimonials, or user-submitted content such as photos, blogs, and writings. **2.) Third-party login functionality:** We allow users with accounts on third-party services, such as Facebook and Google, to log into the Site using functionality that those third parties provide (such as Facebook Connect and Google's OpenID-based authentication mechanism). By using such a functionality to log into the Site, you permit us to access and use specific identifying information related to your third-party account. While these third-party services make a variety of information available, TickPick will only associate your email address or other unique user account identifier with your TickPick account and will not provide the third-party service with any particulars of your TickPick account.  We also allow you to integrate various functionalities from third-party services with TickPick. If you choose to take advantage of this integration feature, we will ask you for your login credentials for the third-party services. By providing those credentials, you are agreeing that we can access and store the information that the third-party site's functionality contains, including personally identifiable information. **3.) Information you give to us:** When you register and/or buy or sell tickets, we ask you for the following information: name and physical shipping, contact, and payment addresses; email address and telephone number; credit card information; and/or login and password. This information must be provided and kept up-to-date to be a Registered User of this site.  **4.) Use of cookies:** "Cookies" are small files that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a TickPick.com customer if you return to TickPick.com using the same computer and browser. We use both "session cookies" and "persistent cookies." Session cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, session cookies expire and no longer have any effect. Persistent cookies are stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time and can be easily removed by following your internet browser's "Help" file directions. We use persistent cookies to enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experiences on our site.  How Is the Information Used? TickPick uses the information you provide to keep enhancing the Site for you, that is, to develop, operate, maintain, enhance, and develop new products. Here are some examples of how we may use the information that you provide or that we collect: We may use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes or to provide the services and customer support you request, and to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems. We may contact you in regard to our Site and updates to our Services, as well as for targeted marketing and promotional offers based on your communication preference. We may use any information we collect to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, to enforce our policies, and to comply with any and all applicable laws. How Is the Information Shared or Disclosed? TickPick may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to: (1) satisfy legal obligations or comply with legal processes (such as a subpoena served on TickPick); (2) protect TickPick and others from fraudulent, abusive, predatory, or unlawful uses or activity; (3) investigate and defend TickPick against any legal claims or threats; (4) protect and defend the rights or property of TickPick; (5) take action on user complaints; or (6) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TickPick, the Site, or the public. We share information between Buyers and Sellers that is required to complete a ticket sale, including name, shipping address, and other information that might be included on the ticket. We do not share a Buyer's credit or debit card information with Sellers. We share your personal information with: Third party service providers that help with our business operations such as fraud detection, credit card processing, delivery services, ticket cancel and reissue, and/or bill collection.  Marketing and/or co-brand partners for certain sites, events, or listings, if you agree during checkout that you would like your information shared for such marketing purposes. We may share your contact information and transaction data (excluding credit card numbers) with the marketing or co-brand partner identified during checkout. Information shared with a marketing or co-brand partner is subject to their privacy policy. We do not control the privacy policies of marketing partners and we encourage you to review their privacy policies.  If there is a change in ownership of TickPick, including through a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to another entity, we may sell or otherwise transfer all information you provide to us, including personally identifiable information, to that entity. Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others We may allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and in applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Application or Site and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked, information about your location, and conversion information. This information may be used by TickPick and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and to deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Site and Application and other websites and applications. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for interest-based advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. Your device may also include a feature (�Limit Ad Tracking� on iOS or �Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads� on Android) that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through applications used for interest-based advertising purposes. See �Your Choices� below for information about how to control the collection of location information by TickPick. The Security of Your Information TickPick employs various physical, managerial, and technical safeguards that are designed to help protect the integrity and security of our systems and to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personally identifiable information that we control. For example, we scramble your password during transmission and limit the employees who can access personally identifiable information to a small set who need such information to perform their jobs. These measures notwithstanding, TickPick is not in a position to guarantee the security of user information, and absolves itself of any responsibility for any security breach that may occur, to the fullest extent of the law. If TickPick learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically, either by email on via our website, so that you can take appropriate protective steps. These methods of communicating with you are only examples. We retain the right to decide which method we will use to notify you of a security breach, and will do so consistent with our legal obligations. Your California Privacy Rights California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at support@tickpick.com. How Long Do We Keep Your Personal Data For? Personal data that we process for any purpose as explained herein shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes, or until your account is deleted - whichever comes first. Notwithstanding the foregoing, TickPick may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your interests or the interests of another person or entity. Ways You Can Access, Control, And Correct Your Personal Information We respect your right to access, correct, request deletion or request restriction of our usage of your personal information as required by applicable law. You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing in to your account. Please update your personal information immediately if it changes or is inaccurate. Keep in mind, once you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it. We will honor any statutory right you might have to access, modify or erase your personal information. To request access and to find out whether any fees may apply, if permitted by applicable national laws, please contact us following the instructions in the Contact Us section below. Where you have a statutory right to request access or request the modification or erasure of your personal information, we can still withhold that access or decline to modify or erase your personal information in some cases in accordance with applicable national laws. If you request that we stop processing some or all of your personal information or you withdraw (where applicable) your consent for our use or disclosure of your personal information for purposes set out in this privacy notice, we might not be able to provide you all of the Services and customer support offered to our users and authorized under this privacy notice and our User Agreement. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable national laws. Where We Operate Our servers and data centers are located in the United States. If you choose to use the Site from outside the U.S., then you should know that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of your region and into the U.S. for storage and processing. By providing your personally identifiable information to us through your use of the Site, you agree to that transfer, storage, and processing in the U.S. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Site. You should know that each region can have its own privacy and data-security laws, some of which may be less stringent than your own region. How To Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or other privacy concerns, you can email us at support@TickPick.com. Please do not include any sensitive information in your email. You can also write us at: TickPick  
ATTN: Privacy Policy Team  
255 W 34th Street #1708  
New York, New York 10122  
Terms and Conditions We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. If we substantially revise the policy (and we will use our discretion to determine if the revision is substantial), we may send emails to our registered users containing a link to the updated policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. If you continue to use our Site after we post an update to this Privacy Policy, this will indicate your acceptance of the update.
